Finding Aid for the Waldo Salt Papers, 1936-1987
UCLA Library, Performing Arts Special Collections
- PROJECTS
  - WISHING WELL/ 15 WORDS
      - Drawings, hand-written and typed notes, n.d. (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - WOMEN'S BARRACKS
      - Script, with annotations and corrections, various pagings. n.d. (Box 119, Folder 3)
      - Script by Jacques Remy and Joseph Morhaim; adaptation by A.Behrstock (pseudonym for W.Salt) and A.S.Cooper. [1955]. 120p. (Box 119, Folder 4)
      - Script; no mention of author. Note on cover: "Property of Damon Productions, Inc., New York City". n.d. 124p. (Box 119, Folder 5)
      - Script by Arthur Behrstock (W.Salt's pseudonym) and A.S.Cooper. Note on cover: "screen adaptation by Nato De Angeles from the book by Tereska Torres". n.d. 122p. (Box 119, Folder 6)
      - Script materials. Incl: typed and hand-written notes on plot and structure, and uncollated script pages. n.d. (Box 120, Folder 1)
      - Outline of novel by Tereska Torres and outline for screenplay, n.d., 2 versions (19 and 25p); treatment by Jacques Remy, n.d., 83p; treatment by Edmund Tezcinski, n.d., 40p. (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - WOODES ROGERS (TV series)
      - Outline for episode "The Parson's Son", n.d., 2p. Note on page 1: "MLD #1" (Mel Davenport, pseudonym). (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence with producers (Sapphire Films Ltd.) regarding scripts for TV series project, 1956-58. (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - WORDS, WORDS, WORDS
      - Theatrical sketch, by "Chablis," n.d., typed script, 8p. (Box 74, Folder 6)
- CORRESPONDENCE
  - ATHERTON, WILLIAM
      - Manuscript letter by William Atherton, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - BAIRD, BIL
      - Manuscript letter by Bil Baird, n.d.; drawing, signed "Bil", n.d. (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - BIRD, TOM
      - Three typed letters by Tom Bird, Artistic Director Vietnam Veterans Ensemble Theatre, 8/16/84, 10/4/85 and 8/4/86. (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - BIRNKRANT, ARTHUR & RUTH
      - Manuscript letter by Ruth and Arthur Birnkrant, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - BLACK, KAREN
      - Note and telegram from Karen Black regarding a project with Arthur Penn, June 1984; photocopy of advertisement from "Variety", 7/1/83, congratulating K.Black. 3 items. (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - BRESLIN, CATHERINE
      - Two manuscript letters by Catherine Breslin, [1980]. (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - CORMILLOT, ALBERTO
      - Typed letter by Alberto Cormillot, 9/20/73, incl. two photos with W.Salt. (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - DEUTSCH, DAVID
      - Typed letter by David Deutsch, 12/2/80, regarding film project; typed letter [by Victor Wilmer], about the same topic, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - FONDA, JANE
      - Card signed "Jane" [Fonda], n.d. (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - FRIENDS
      - Christmas, birthday and anniversary cards, notes and telegrams from various friends and acquaintances, various dates. 11 items. (Box 81, Folder 14)
  - FROUZA, SIMON
      - Typed letter signed "Simon" [Frouza], 4/3/86, incl. photocopy of author's trips in the U.S. 3 items. (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - GINNES, ABRAM
      - Telegram and letter from Abram S. Ginnes, 5/23/69 and 11/1/71. (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - HALPRIN, LAURENCE
      - Leaflet with program designed by Laurence Halprin to visit San Francisco. 3 items. (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - HARMON, SIDNEY
      - Typed letter by Sidney Harmon, incl. photocopy of poem and invitation to exhibit, 9/15/83. 4 items. (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - HECHT, HAROLD
      - Manuscript letter by Harold Hecht proposing W.Salt to write "The Son of the Crimson Pirate", n.d. (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence
      - Photocopies and originals of correspondence concerning controversy over credits for "The Crimson Pirate" and effects of blacklist on W.Salt and other screenwriters, January-May 1952. 20 items. (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - HELLMAN, JEROME
      - Correspondence with producer Jerome Hellman regarding "Coming Home", "The Day of the Locust", "The Lonely Passion of Judith Hearne", etc, incl. photocopy of letters to Joseph Losey (8/22/73) and critic Charles Champlin, 1969-77. 17 items. (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - HILLMANN, ROBERT L.
      - Letter of recommendation for Robert H. Hillman to the John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundations, [February 1986]. (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - HUNT, MARSHA
      - Typed letter by Marsha Hunt, 7/10/84. (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - JARRICO, PAUL
      - Typed and hand-written letters by Paul Jarrico, regarding personal matters and HUAC-related activities, incl. a profile of W.Salt [possibly by P.Jarrico], 1952-80. 11 items. (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - JOHNSON, BUFFIE
      - Typed and hand-written letters by Buffie Johnson, 1982-83. 5 items. (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - JOSH, DANIEL
      - Typed letter by Josh Daniel, describing film project, n.d.; response by W.Salt, 11/5/85. (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - LIM, GENNY
      - Typed letter by Genny Lim, 10/18/85; two letters of recommendation for her by W.Salt, addressed to the National Endowment for the Arts, 4/5/84, and the John Simon Guggenheim Foundation, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - THE LIVING THEATER
      - Two typed and manuscript letters by Julian Beck and Judith Malina, members of The Living Theater, thanking W.Salt for his contribution towards their release from prison in Brazil, 9/4/71. (Box 81, Folder 15)
  - LOSEY, JOSEPH
      - Correspondence with Joseph Losey regarding "Courier to Peking" and "Save Me the Waltz" projects, and discussing producer Jerome Hellman's participation in them, 1973-1974. 7 items. (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - LUMI, MARIKA
      - Correspondence with Marika Lumi regarding Memorandum of Agreement between her and Jennorah Productions, Inc. (W.Salt) to develop project based on book "The Kin of Ata", July-September 1982. 6 items. (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - MACLAINE, SHIRLEY
      - Manuscript card by Shirley MacLaine, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - MCDANIEL, CHARLES A.
      - Typed letter by Charles A. McDaniel, incl. photocopy of typed article by the author, 4/7/87. (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - MICHEL, DEE
      - Two typed and manuscript letters by Dee Michel, incl. clipping, n.d. and 8/2/81. (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - MICHEL, GUY
      - Typed letter by Guy Michel, incl. postcards, drawings and clippings, n.d. (Box 80, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence with Guy Michel regarding magazine "Art Maggots", n.d., incl. clippings, photocopies and original artwork, issues of magazine and calendar. (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - O'CONNELL, SUSAN
      - Typed letter by Susan O'Connell, 7/17/78. (Box 80, Folder 39)
  - POWELL, MICHAEL
      - Manuscript letter by British director Michael Powell addressed to "Mr.Davenport" (pseudonym), concerning the filming of W.Salt's script "Never Turn Your Back on a Friend", 12/22/63. (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - PUTTNAM, DAVID
      - Photocopy of congratulatory from W.Salt to David Puttnam; W.Salt mentions his poor health and medical advice not to work, 2/18/87. (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - ROBINSON, EARL
      - Typed and manuscript letters and postcards by Earl Robinson, incl. clippings, l959-1981. 19 items. (Box 80, Folder 43)
      - Typed and manuscript letters and cards by Earl Robinson, incl. clippings, n.d. 17 items. (Box 80, Folder 44)
      - Letters from the Earl Robinson Foundation, March 1981-February 1982. 7 items. (Box 80, Folder 45)
  - ROSENBAUM, NINA
      - Typed letter by documentary filmmaker Nina Rosenbaum, seeking support for film project, 10/30/85. Incl. clippings of her film career and material related to the project. 7 items. (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - SALO, MATTI
      - Two typed letters by Matti Salo -Finnish Film Archive-, concerning his research for book on blacklisted writers, 7/26/85 and 11/14/85; letter by W.Salt providing information, 1/5/85. (Box 81, Folder 6)
  - SALT -A STORY ABOUT A FILM
      - Three letters by Marine Dominguez and Lisa D. Kernan regarding film project about the making of the 1954 "Salt of the Earth", l984-86. 9 items. (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - SAVE ME THE WALTZ
      - Correspondence with Joseph Losey and Jerome Hellman regarding film project "Save me the Waltz", August 1972-April 1973. 8 items. (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - SCHLESINGER, JOHN
      - Three typed letters by John Schlesinger regarding "Coming Home" and "The Day of the Locust", 5/1/70, 7/7/71 and 4/20/72; manuscript letter by J.Schlesinger, n.d.; copy of letter by Jerome Hellman to J.Schlesinger concerning various projects, 7/13/70. (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - SPANISH REFUGEES
      - Report and brochure from Eric G.Muggeridge-Foster Parents'Plan for Spanish Children; three manuscript letters, in Spanish with typed English version, by child refuggee Juan Campuzano Solanas, incl. his photo, 7/27/39, 10/28/39, 12/11/39. 11 items. (Box 81, Folder 9)
  - STEFFENS, ROGER
      - Two typed letters by Roger Steffens, Vietnam veteran, 6/25/75 and 2/24/76, incl. clipping; letter by Richard G.Hofman, also a Vietnam veteran, 4/10/79. (Box 81, Folder 7)
  - TRUMBO, DALTON
      - Letter by Dalton Trumbo, congratulating W.Salt on "Midnight Cowboy", 2/16/70. (Box 81, Folder 10)
  - VAN LIEU, FELIX
      - Two letters by W.Salt to the Social Security Administration regarding the use of pen names "M.L.Davenport -Marion Lewis Davenport" and "Felix Van Lieu", July 29 and October 11, l957; invoices, receipts, etc, using these pseudonyms, l959-60. (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - WARNER BROS.
      - Letter by Frank Daugherty, assistant story editor at Warner Bros., suggesting W.Salt's play "Art in Gotham", submitted to the studio, be turned into a magazine short story, 10/9/35. (Box 81, Folder 12)
  - WYLER, CATHERINE
      - Typed letter by Catherine Wyler, n.d. (Box 81, Folder 13)
- HOUSE UN-AMERICAN ACTIVITIES COMMITTEE
  - HOUSE UN-AMERICAN ACTIVITIES COMMITTEE
      - Telegrams and subpoenas to appear before the HUAC, dated 11/19/47 and 2/17/51. 4 items. (Box 77, Folder 1)
      - Transcript of hearings: Testimony of Howard Da Silva and Gale Sondergaard, 3/21/51, 31p. (Box 77, Folder 2)
      - Transcript of hearings: Testimony of Richard Collins, 4/12/51, 101p. (Box 77, Folder 3)
      - Transcript of hearings: Testimony of Waldo Salt, 4/13/51, 38p. (Box 77, Folder 4)
      - Transcript of hearings: Testimony of Meta Reis Rosenberg, 4/13/51, 30p. (Box 77, Folder 5)
      - Transcript of hearings: Testimony of Paul Jarrico, 4/13/51, 17p. (Box 77, Folder 6)
      - Transcript of hearings: Testimony of Robert Lees, n.d., 32p. (Box 77, Folder 7)
      - Transcript of hearings: Testimony of Victor Killian, n.d., 4p. (Box 77, Folder 8)
      - Transcript of hearings: Testimony of Alfred Levitt, n.d., 8p. Letter from A.Levitt to W.Salt and Mary Davenport Salt, 10/19/51. (Box 77, Folder 9)
      - Two statements by W.Salt, n.d., 1 and 4p. (Box 77, Folder 10)
      - Newspaper clippings concerning actor Larry Parks' testimony before HUAC, March-April 1951. Three typed articles on L.Parks' case, n.d., no author. Hand-written notes on index cards. (Box 77, Folder 11)
      - Copies of statement and declarations regarding HUAC, n.d., no author. 4 items. (Box 77, Folder 12)
      - Letters and telegrams to W.Salt from family and friends regarding his testimony before HUAC, April 1951. 9 items. (Box 77, Folder 13)
      - Pamphlets, leaflets, legislation, invitations, regarding HUAC activities and freedom of speech. 11 items. (Box 77, Folder 14)
      - Newspaper clippings regarding HUAC hearings, 1951. (Box 77, Folder 15)
      - Issues of "Variety" and "The Hollywood Reporter" refering to HUAC hearings, October 1950-September l951. 42 copies. (Box 77, Folder 16)
      - Diploma honoring W.Salt after the HUAC hearings, n.d. (Box 77, Folder 17)
      - Material relating to the l947-48 HUAC hearings. Incl: statement by Berthold Brecht; excerpts from speeches on freedom, 11/16/47; leaflet with Ring Lardner, Jr., declarations; program of testimonial dinner, 2/27/48; etc. 9 items. (Box 77, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence regarding HUAC and the blacklist, 1957-83. Incl: letters from Fred Rinaldo, 9/1/57; Anne Revere, 2/16/57; Nancy Schwartz, 6/25/76; Lester Cole, 4/26/79; Ring Lardner, Jr., 2/25/81; etc. 13 items. (Box 77, Folder 19)
      - Miscellaneous material, incl. newspaper clipping on W.Salt and the blacklist, Los Angeles Times, 2/10/70; typed and hand-written notes; drafts and copies of speeches. 8 items. (Box 77, Folder 20)
      - Legal correspondence with attorney Jerome B.Lurie regarding W.Salt's affidavit submitted to the House of Representatives Committee on Un-American Activities, October 1963-January 1964. 7 items. (Box 77, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence regarding activities of the Actors Laboratory, Hollywood, in connection with the HUAC investigations, 1948. Copies of three plays, promoted by the Actors' Laboratory. 13 items. (Box 83, Folder 1)
- PROFESSIONAL ACTIVITIES
  - A.C.L.U. - AMERICAN CIVIL LIBERTIES UNION
      - Correspondence and publications by the A.C.L.U. and other related organizations, 1983-86. 9 items. (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - ACADEMY OF MOTION PICTURE ARTS AND SCIENCES
      - Correspondence with the Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences regarding membership, reception of Oscar, Academy publication, 1970-86; brochures and report. 11 items. (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - THE AMERICAN WRITERS CONGRESS
      - Correspondence regarding the organization of the American Writers Congress-1981, incl. program, invitation, clippings, hand-written note by W.Salt, August-October 1981. 8 items. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - BEIJING FILM ACADEMY
      - Beijing Film Academy members' visit to New York University, 1984, incl. cards, list of visitors and clipping. 8 items. (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - THE DRAMATISTS GUILD
      - Correspondence with the Dramatists Guild, incl. copy of constitution, newsletters, sample of contract, information of meetings and activities, 1986. 9 items. (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - INTERNATIONAL PLATFORM ASSOCIATION
      - Publicity material from International Platform Association, 1985. 4 items. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - LECTURES AND SEMINARS
      - Correspondence, copies of speeches and notes concerning lectures, talks and seminars given by W.Salt, 1974-1986. 29 items. (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - Hand-written notes outlining lecture on film, n.d. (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Twenty two typed and manuscript letters requesting and thanking W.Salt's participation in lectures, seminars and related activities, 1973-1983. (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - MILL VALLEY FILM FESTIVAL
      - Correspondence regarding W.Salt's participation in the Mill Valley Film Festival, September 20-29, 1984, incl. program, tickets, cards and clippings. 28 items. (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - NEW YORK UNIVERSITY -SCHOOL OF THE ARTS
      - Letters, memos and students evaluations from the Institute of Film and Television, School of the Arts, New York University, regarding W.Salt's appointment as professor, 1977-1985. 15 items. (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Letter from the New York Council of the Arts, Sciences and Professions, concerning W.Salt's nomination to the Executive Board, 5/21/52. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - OFFICE OF THE AMERICAS (O.O.A.)
      - Two issues of "Focus", newsletter of O.O.A.-Office of the Americas; O.O.A. letter signed by actor Martin Sheen inviting new members, n.d.; flyer inviting to screening of film "Latino", [1985]. 4 items. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - PALO ALTO COMMUNITY PLAYERS
      - Three typed and manuscript letters regarding the Palo Alto Community Players activities, 1980-82; clippings and programs, various dates. 10 items. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - PEN AMERICAN CENTER
      - Two typed letters and newsletter from the Pen American Center, incl. invitation to attend "Forbidden Writers" program, 11/22/85 and 6/10/86. (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - STAGE - ACTOR/DIRECTOR/WRITER
      - Program sheets of theatrical events at Stanford University, in which W.Salt participated as author and actor, 1931-35. 6 items. (Box 114, Folder 10)
      - Programs of stage productions "Hay Fever" and "The Dover Road", directed by W.Salt at the Menlo Junior College, incl. college newspaper. 1935. 5 items. (Box 114, Folder 11)
      - Programs of stage productions of "The Cock Crows" and "The Pursuit of Happiness", in which W.Salt participated as an actor and stage manager, l936. 5 items. (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - STANFORD ALUMNI ASSOCIATION
      - Typed note, 7/28/70, and card signed Pat McGilligan, regarding Stanford Alumni reunion, incl. newsletter and reunion program. (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - SUNDANCE INSTITUTE
      - Correspondence with the Sundance Institute regarding W.Salt's participation in the June Laboratory for filmmakers, incl. list of participants, schedule of activities, brochure, etc, May-December l981. 14 items. (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence with the Sundance Institute regarding W.Salt's impossibility to participate in the June Laboratory for filmmakers, due to his health condition, March-July 1982, incl. course material, newsletter and clipping. 11 items. (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence with the Sundance Institute regarding W.Salt's participation in the June Laboratory for filmmakers, incl. list of participants, schedule of activities, brochure, newsletter, etc, January-November 1983. 9 items. (Box 83, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence with the Sundance Institute regarding W.Salt's participation in the June Laboratory for filmmakers, incl. list of participants, schedule of activities, brochure, cards, etc, January-December 1984. 21 items. (Box 84, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence with the Sundance Institute regarding W.Salt's participation in the June Laboratory for filmmakers, incl. list of participants, schedule of activities, brochures, letters from participants, clipping, etc, March-December 1985. 18 item (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence with the Sundance Institute regarding W.Salt's participation in the June Laboratory for filmmakers, incl. list of participants, schedule of activities, brochures, Producers seminar materials, clippings, cards, May-Sept 1986. 31 items. (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Brochure of the United States Film Festival. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - UNION OF CONCERNED SCIENTISTS
      - Two newsletters and one brochure from the Union of Concerned Scientists, 1985-86. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - WRITERS' CONGRESS
      - Transcript of radio interview with W.Salt regarding the 1943 Writers' Congress, Los Angeles, 11/2/43, 10p; copy of speech delivered in Royce Hall, Univ. of California, Los Angeles, n.d., 8p. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - WRITERS GUILD OF AMERICA
      - Correspondence with the Writers Guild of America regarding Laurel Award, incl. speech, drafts, clipping and W.Salt nomination of Ring Lardner, Jr., as 1987 recipient. 4 items. January-May 1986. (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence with the Writers Guild of America, 1970-86: summaries of meetings; list of members; correspondence and hand-written notes for W.G.A San Dimas Conference, l970; correspondence regarding copies of W.Salt's screenplays. 34 items. (Box 84, Folder 8)
- PERSONAL MATERIALS
  - ARTWORK
      - Drawings by W.Salt (pencil, ink, watercolor) n.d. Unnumbered. (Box 122, Folder 1)
      - Gladys Schwartz' sketch-book, containing drawings and sketches (ink, pencil and watercolor). n.d. Inscribed by W.Salt. (Box 122, Folder 2)
      - Drawings by Gladys Schwartz (ink and pencil). Some are dated 1976. Unnumbered. (Box 122, Folder 3)
      - Drawings by Gladys Schwartz (ink and pencil). n.d. Unnumbered. (Box 122, Folder 4)
      - Drawings by W.Salt (ink, pencil and charcoal). Note [by W.Salt]: "50s mostly; sketch class on 28th St. loft NYC w/Zero Mostel, Kallem brothers, Ian Hunter, etc; and Gladys Schwartz' studio on 104th St.". Unnumbered. (Box 123, Folder -)
      - Drawings by W.Salt (ink, pencil and charcoal). Note [by W.Salt]: "sketches 40s, 50s and 60s". Unnumbered. (Box 124, Folder -)
      - Drawings and cartoons by W.Salt (ink, pencil, charcoal, etc). n.d. Unnumbered. (Box 125, Folder -)
      - Drawings, sketches, watercolors, etc, by William Salt, Sr. (W.Salt's father), and Gladys Schwartz. Mostly undated. Unnumbered. (Box 127, Folder -)
  - AWARDS
      - Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences: Certificate of Appreciation to W.Salt for service to the Academy, n.d. (Box 117, Folder -)
  - BIOGRAPHICAL INFORMATION
      - W.Salt's obituary from Los Angeles Times, Los Angeles Herald Examiner, "Variety", etc; biographical data for "Who's Who in America". 8 items. (Box 114, Folder 1)
      - Clippings and photocopies of articles regarding W.Salt'career, various dates. 11 items. (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - FAMILY PAPERS
      - Birth certificate of Ambur [sic, Amber?] Arvilla Dana, W.Salt's wife, issued 1939. (Box 91, Folder 5)
      - Newspaper clippings (l975, 1986), note, drawing, mimeographed book, regarding David Greenberg, W.Salt's son-in-law. 6 items. (Box 91, Folder 6)
      - Note from Jonah Salt Greeenberg, W.Salt's grandson, and invitation to attend Grandparents' Day at his school, 1984. (Box 91, Folder 7)
      - Letters, cards, and notes to W.Salt from his daughter Deborah, 1960-86. 47 items. (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Newspaper and magazine clippings (1978, 1985), booklets, catalogue, etc, regarding Deborah Salt's career as a painter. 9 items. (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Drawings, collage, reproduction of works, etc., by Deborah Salt. 12 items. (Box 91, Folder 10)
      - Poems by Deborah Salt (197l), clippings, school report and publication incl. cover illustration and poem by her. 6 items. (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Speech for W.Salt and Eve Merriam's wedding ceremony, with annotations, dated 10/22/83. (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Legal correspondence regarding separation agreement between W.Salt and Eve Merriam, 1985-86. 3 items. (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Statement of assets and liabilities corresponding to W.Salt and Eve Merriam Salt, 5/31/84. 2 copies. (Box 91, Folder 14)
      - Poems, clippings (1978,1982), and theater programs regarding Eve Merriam's professional activities. 7 items. (Box 92, Folder 1)
      - Letter and card signed Dee Michel, 1981, and notes. 4 items. (Box 92, Folder 2)
      - Letters, cards and telegram to W.Salt from his daughter Jennifer, 1962-67; correspondence from Sarah Lawrence college, 1966; etc. 14 items. (Box 92, Folder 3)
      - Newspaper and magazine clippings (1969-78), theater programs, regarding Jennifer Salt's career as an actress. 17 items. (Box 92, Folder 4)
      - Letters by Mary Davenport, W.Salt's wife, 1965-67. 11 items. (Box 92, Folder 5)
      - Poems by Mary Davenport, incl. letter addressed to "Gladys" [Schwartz?], 3/10/79. (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - W.Salt's personal documents, 1925-69. Incl: three passports; birth, marriage and divorce certificates; communication from the Office of War, 1945; etc. 8 items. (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Legal correspondence regarding W.Salt's will, 1981-84. 8 items. (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Invitation to attend retirement dinner in honor of W.Salt's brother William, 1970; obituary and clippings of his funeral, 1972; etc. 6 items. (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Bank statements, death certificate (1950), funeral expenses, insurance certificate, etc. regarding W.Salt's father, William Haslem Salt. 12 items. (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - Legal correspondence regarding the estate of Winnie Shimp Salt -W.Salt's mother-, 1963. 3 items. (Box 93, Folder 4)
      - Letters, cards and drawings by W.Salt's wife Gladys Schwartz, undated. 12 items. (Box 93, Folder 5)
      - Scrap book (1977) and typed script, "Escape to America -(A Part) Autobiography and Letters" (l969), from Gladys Schwartz's parents, Simon and Anna, to W.Salt. (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, catalogues, cards, etc., related to Gladys Schwartz' art exhibits and gallery showings, 1975-81. 55 items. (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Memorial speech [by Lee] in honor of Gladys Schwartz Salt, [1980]. 2 copies. (Box 93, Folder 8)